He has to break his curse before she breaks his heart.
Good Luck Chuck is a comedy, romance film directed by Mark Helfrich.
Cursed since childhood, dentist Charlie Logan cannot find the right woman.
Even worse, he learns that each of his ex-girlfriends finds true love with
the man she meets after her relationship with him ends.
Hearing of Charlie's reputation as a good-luck charm, women
from all over line up for a quick tryst.
But when Charlie meets the woman of his dreams, he must find a way to
break the curse or risk losing her to the next man she meets.
Dr. Charlie Logan, played by Dane Cook.
Cam Wexler, played by Jessica Alba.
Dr. Stu Klaminsky, played by Dan Fogler.
Reba, played by Ellia English.
Joe, played by Lonny Ross.
Young Stu, played by Troy Gentile.
Good Luck Chuck is a 2007 romantic comedy film directed by Mark Helfrich,
written by Josh Stolberg, and starring Dane Cook and Jessica Alba.
In the film, women find their "one true love" after
having sex with a dentist named Chuck (Cook).
Chuck meets a girl named Cam (Alba) and tries to become her true love.
Good Luck Chuck was the directorial debut of Helfrich, a long-time film editor.
It was released in theaters on September 21, 2007, by
Lionsgate, and was panned by critics.
Despite this, it grossed $59.8 million against a $25 million budget.
One of its theatrical posters parodied the well-known Rolling Stone cover photographed
by Annie Leibovitz featuring John Lennon and Yoko Ono in similar poses.
The film explores themes of aquarium, bride, man woman
relationship, one-night stand, love.
The tone is lighthearted and emotional.